NAA Committee Files 6205
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NAA Committee Files
1947-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Academy of Arbitrators (NAA)
6205
18 cubic feet
18 linear ft.
Records.
8258617
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 04, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6136: Dennis Nolan Collection of National Academy of Arbitrators History Files 5985: NAA Additional Files Regarding Proceedings 5796: NAA Additional Records 6004: NAA Additional Records 6004 AV: NAA Audio-Visual Material 5775: NAA Records 6004 OHM: NAA History Committee Oral History Interview Masters 6004 OHT: NAA History Committee Oral History Interview Transcripts 6205: NAA Committee Files 5246: NAA Records
National Academy of Arbitrators
8258617
- Arbitration Cases, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Robert Meiners/Raymond Sherwood
- Regional Chairs, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Disability Insurance- Theodore K. High, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Legal Representation- Amicus Participation, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Nominating- Howard H. Block, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Regional Chairs, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Research- Mario F. Boganno, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Academy History- James L. Stern, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Auditing- George Nicolau, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Board Dinners, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Chronicle- Tia S. Denenberg, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Committee Appointments and Chairs, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Contract: Fremont State, North Dakota, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Coordinator/Regional Activities- James J. Sherman, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Designating Agency Liaison- Lewis M. Gill, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Development/New Arbitrators- Theodore St. Antoine, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Dues Waiver Policy- John Dunsford, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Executive Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Future Meeting Arrangements- Nicholas Zumas, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Intern Training- Lewis R. Amis, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Law and Legislation- Marlin M. Volz, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Legal Affairs- George E. Bowles, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Legal Representation- Nathan Lipson, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- New Member Orientation- Mark L. Kahn, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Officers & Board of Governors, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Officers & Board of Governors- Dallas L. Jones, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Overseas Correspondents- Alvin L. Goldman, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Policy Handbook- James C. Duff, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Policy Memo Regarding Membership, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- President- William P. Murphy, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Professional Responsibility & Grievances- Arthur Stark, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Publications- Gladys W. Gruenberg, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Public Employment Disputes Settlement- Robert G. Howlett, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Regional Chairs, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Research- Clifford E. Smith, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Speaker/Spouse Expenses, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Special Committee- Executive Directors- Clare B. McDermott, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Special Committee On Professionalism- Ralph Seward, Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Academy History- Gladys W. Gruenberg, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Arrangements- 1987 Annual Meeting-John F. Caraway, Chair, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Board of Governors, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Chronicle, The, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Code- Mittenthal, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Committee Chairs, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Committee Appointments, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Designating Agency Liaison- Lewis M. Gill, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Development of New Arbitrators, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Executive Director, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Executive Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Future Meeting Arrangements, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- International Studies- Alvin L. Goldman, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Intern Training- Lewis R. Amis, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Investment Committee- Raymond L. Britton, Chair, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Iowa State University/Computing Services for research Com., 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Legal Affairs- George R. Fleischli, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Legal Representation, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Liaison Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- National Coordinator Regional Activities- Francis Bairstow, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Nominating- Anthony V. Sinicropi, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- President- Arvid Anderson, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Professionalism, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Publications- Gladys W. Gruenberg, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Public Employment Disputes Settlement- Robert G. Howlett, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Regional Chairs, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Research- Clifford E. Smith, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Correspondence [folder 1 of 4], 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Correspondence [folder 2 of 4], 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Correspondence [folder 3 of 4], 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Correspondence [folder 4 of 4], 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Amicus Brief- S.D. Warren II, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Arrangements- 1988 Annual Meeting- Mark Thompson, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Auditing- Mark L. Kahn, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Coordinator/Regional Activities- Frances Bairstow, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Designating Agency Liaison- Eva Robins, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Executive Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- History- Gladys W. Gruenberg, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Inter-Committee Relations & Functions- Howard A. Block, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Intern Training- Lewis R. Amis, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Kindness, Michael, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Law & Legislation- Marlin M Volz, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Legal Affairs- George R. Fleischli, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Legal Representation- Nathan Lipson, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Liaison Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Members Designate- May '89, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Michigan, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- New Member Orientation- John E. Dunsford, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- President- Thomas T. Roberts, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Program- 1988 Annual Meeting- James L. Stern, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Publications- Gladys W. Gruenberg, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Public Employment Disputes Settlement- Walter L. Eisenberg, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Radisson Hotel, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Regional Chairs, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Research- Clifford E. Smith, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Semi-annual Admissions- M. Kahn, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- 1990 Annual Meeting, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Arrangements, 1990 Annual Meeting- Kenneth A. Parea, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Auditing- Mark L. Kahn, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Chronicle, The- C. Chester Brisco, Managing Editor, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Chronicle- Searches in the Workplace- Duty to Disclose, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Committee Chairs, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Continuing Education- Jay E. Grenig, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Continuing Education Arrangement- Edward Parker Archer, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Designating Agency Liaison- Claire B. McDermott, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Executive Committee- Alfred C. Dybeck, President, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Free Airline Tickets, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Future Meeting Arrangements- Nicholas H. Zumas, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- History- Gladys W. Gruenberg, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- International Studies- J. Joseph Loewenberg, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Intern Training Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Law and Legislation- Ronald F. Talarico, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Legal Affairs- Gerorge R. Fleischli, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Legal Representation- Nathan Lipson, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Michigan- Mario Chiesa, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- New Directions and Functions/Chronicle- Edgar A. Jones, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Nominating- Nilton Rubin, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Officers and Board of Governors, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- President- Alfred C. Dybeck, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- President-elect- Howard Block, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Proceedings, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Professionalism Programs- Walter J. Gershenfeld, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Program, 1990 Annual Meeting- Anthony V. Sinicropi, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Publications- Gladys W. Gruenberg, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Public Employment Dispute Settlement- Walter L. Eisenberg, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Regional Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Research- Mario F. Boganno, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Review Inter-committee Relations & Functions- Howard S. Block, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Society of Professionals in Dispute Resolution (SPIDR)- Commission on Qualifications, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- States Accreditation, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Tribunal Appeals- Patrick J. Fisher, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Academy Governance- Benjamin Aaron, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Annual Meeting, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Annual Proceedings Editor- Gladys W. Gruenberg, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Auditing Committee- Mark L. Kahn, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Board of Governors (1 of 2), 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Board of Governors (2 of 2), 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Chronicle, The- Chester Brisco, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Chronicle Consultative- Edgar A. Jones, Jr., 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Committees Chronicle, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Continuing Education- Jay E. Grenig, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Coordinator Regional Activities- Mario Chiesa, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Deaths Prior to 6/1/90, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Designating Agency- Liaison Committee Clare B. McDermott, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Executive Committee- Howard S. Block, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Honorary Life Members, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Honorary Membership- William P. Murphy, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- If Any With Regard to Alternative Labor Dispute Resolution Procedures- Michael H. Beck, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- International Studies- J. Joseph Loewenberg, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Law & Legislation- Ronald F. Talarico, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Legal Representation- Timothy J. Heinsz, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Long Range Program Planning- Richard Mittenthal, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Meeting Agenda & Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Members Designate, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Membership Directory Policy Committee- Michael Beck, Chair, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Minutes- Reports to 90 With Them, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- New Member Orientation- Eva Robins, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Nominating Committee- Raymond Goetz, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Obituaries and Milestones, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- President Howard S. Block, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- President-elect Anthony V. Sinicropi, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Professionalism Programs- Walter J. Gershenfeld, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Program- Annual Meeting- Richard I. Block, Chair, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Public Employment Disputes Settlement- Walter L. Eisenberg, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Regional Chairs, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Reinstatement of Suspended Members, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Research Committee- Mario F. Boganno, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Tribunal Appeals, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Academy History- Dennis R. Nolan, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Annual Business Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Annual Proceedings Editor- Gladys W. Gruenberg, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Board of Governors- Anthony V. Sinicropi, President, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Board of Governors- Reports (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Board of Governors- Reports (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Chronicle, The- Gil Vernon, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Committee on Academy Governance- Benjamin Aaron, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Committee on Dues Waiver Policy- Mark Thompson, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Committee to Review the Salary of the Secretary- Edward B. Krinsky, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Continuing Education- William H. Holley, Jr., 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Continuing Regional Education- Mario Chiesa, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Coordinator Regional Activities- Mario Chiesa, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Designating Agency Liaison Committee- Clare B. McDermott, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Executive Committee- Anthony V. Sinicropi, President, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Gender-neutral Terminology- Gladys Gershenfeld, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Honorary Life Member- Ted Weatherill, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- If Any- Alternative Labor Dispute Resolution Procedures- Michael H. Beck, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- International Studies- J. Joseph Loewenberg, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Law & Legislation- Ronald F. Talarico, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Legal Affairs- Gerry Fellman (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Legal Affairs- Gerry Fellman (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Legal Representation- Timothy J. Heinsz, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Long Range Program Planning- Richard Mittenthal, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- New Member Orientation- Eva Robins, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Nominating Committee- Howard D. Brown, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Public Employment Disputes Settlement- Harry Graham, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Preseident Anthony V. Sinicropi, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- President-elect David Feller, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Research Committee- Charles J. Coleman, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Uniform Employment Termination Act- Arvid Anderson, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Correspondence [folder 1 of 4], 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Correspondence [folder 2 of 4], 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Correspondence [folder 3 of 4], 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Correspondence [folder 4 of 4], 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- American Arbitration Association (AAA), 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Auditory Committee- Milton Rubin, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Board of Governors- David E. Feller, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Committee on Academy History- Dennis R. Nolan (1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Committee on Academy History- Dennis R. Nolan (2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Committee on Future Meeting Arrangements, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Committee on Honorary Membership- Arnold Zack, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Committee on International Studies- Paul F. Gilbert, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Committee on Legal Affairs- Gerry L. Fellman, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Committee on Legal Representation- Timothy J. Heinsz, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Committee on Public Employment Dictates Settlement- Harry Graham, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Committee to Consider The Academy's Role, If Any, With Regard to Alternative Labor Dispute Resolution Procedures- Michael H. Beck (1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Committee to Consider The Academy's Role, If Any, With Regard to Alternative Labor Dispute Resolution Procedures- Michael H. Beck (2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Designating Agency Liaison Committee- Thomas T. Roberts, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Law & Legislation- Roger I. Abrams, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Long Range Program Planning- Richard Mittenthal, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Old Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- President David E. Feller (1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- President David E. Feller (2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- President-elect Dallas Jones, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Regional Chairs, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Research Committee- Charles J. Coleman, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Academy History- James Oldham, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Advisory Opinions, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Alternative Labor Dispute Resolution (ALDR) Reports- Michael Beck, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Annual Meeting, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Annual Proceedings- Gladys Gruenberg, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Auditing Committee- Milton Rubin, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Board of Governors (1 of 3), 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Board of Governors (2 of 3), 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Board of Governors (3 of 3), 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Board of Governors Reports- Minneapolis, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Board of Governors Reports- Pittsburgh, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Chronicle, The- Gil Vernon, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Code Revision Committee- Kagel Memo, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Committee on Development of New Arbitrators and Intern Training, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Continuing Education- Sara Adler, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Continuing Education Committee- William H. Holley, Jr., 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Continuing Regional Education- William H. Holley, Jr., 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Continuing Regional Education- Mario Chiesa, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Designating Liaison Committee Reports- Thomas Roberts, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Dues Waiver Policy Reports- Mark Thompson, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Executive Committee- Dallas Jones, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Executive Officer David Feller, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- International Studies Reports- Paul Gerhart, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Jones, Dallas, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Law & Legislation- Roger I. Abrams, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Legal Affairs- Gerry Fellman, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Legal Representation Reimbursement, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Legal Representation Reports- Joe Gentile, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Long Range Program Planning- Richard Mittenthal, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Mexico Project, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- New Member Orientation- Howard Block, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Nominating Committee- Joseph Girolamo, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Pittsburgh- October, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Polh, Stuart [folder 1 of 2], 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Pohl, Stuart [folder 2 of 2], 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- President Dallas Jones, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- President-elect Arnold Zack, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Public Employee Disputes Settlement Reports- Harry Graham, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Region 1- Susan R. Brown, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Region 2- Robert E. Peterson, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Region 3- Stanley J. Schwartz, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Region 4- Robert O. Harris, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Region 5- William Holley, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Region 6- Robert Stevens, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Region 7- Dick Verity, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Region 8- Robert A. Creo, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Rigion 9- Joseph Krislor, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Region 10- Sol M. Elkin, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Region 11- Daniel J. Nielsen, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Region 12- Mark W. Suardi, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Region 13- Francis Quinn, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Region 14- William Rentfro, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Region 15- Thomas Angelo, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Region 16- Mei Laing Bickner, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Region 17- John H. Abernathy, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Regional Activities Coordinator William Holley, Jr., 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Research Committee- Mei Laing Bickner, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Special Committee on Code Revisions- John Kagel, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Special Committee on Continuing Education Conference- Jack Dunsford, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Special Committee on Mediation- Charles Rehmus, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Special Committee on Publication of Awards- Reginald Alleyne, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Board of Governors [folder 1 of 3], 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Academy History- James Oldham, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Annual Proceedings- Joyce M. Najita, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Auditing Committee- Allan McCauseland, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Biographical Sketches (Masters), 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Board of Governors [folder 2 of 3], 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Board of Governors [folder 3 of 3], 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Chronicle, The- Andria Knapp, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Continuing Education- Sara Adler, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Continuing Regional Education- William H. Holley, Jr., 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Executive Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Future Meeting Arrangements- David Petersen, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Honorary Life Memberships- Tony Sinicropi, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- International Studies- Paul Gerhart, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Legal Representation- Joe Gentile, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Legal Representation Reimbursements, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- New Member Orientation- Howard Block, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Nominating Committee- Jim Harkless, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- President Arnold Zack, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- President-elect Ted Weatherill, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Region 2- Howard Edelman, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Region 6- Robert Stevens, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Region 7- Dick Verity, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Region 8- Thomas Hewitt, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Region 9- Earl Curry, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Region 11- Daniel J. Nielsen, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Region 12- Gerald Fowler, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Region 15- Anita Christine Knowlton, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Region 16- Sara Adler, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Research Committee- Mei Laing Bickner, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- AT&T Technologies v. Communications Workers, Local 5090., 1985 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Brief of the National Academy of Arbitrators as Amicus Curiae in Support of Respondent. U.S. Supreme Court 1985. San Francisco: Bowne, n.d. David E. Feller and William J. Fallon.
- Briefs- 1948-1949, Vol. I, CIO Legal Department. (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Briefs- 1948-1952, Vol. II, CIO Legal Department. (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Briefs- 1951-1953, Vol. III, CIO Legal Department. (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Briefs- 1953-1955, Vol. IV, CIO Legal Department. (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Briefs- 1955-1956, Vol. V, Goldberg, Feller & Bredhoff. (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Briefs- 1956-1958, Vol. VI, Goldberg, Feller & Bredhoff. (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Briefs- 1959-1960, Vol. VII, Goldberg, Feller & Bredhoff. (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Briefs- 1960-1961, David E. Feller. (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Briefs- 1962-1963, David E. Feller. (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Briefs- 1964-1966, David E. Feller. (Box 17, Folder 5)